A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2 FA925
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Editorial Correspondence, 2
  - GP #2091: D. Ottoson, E. Albuquerque, S. Chung (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - GP #2092: L. Thomas, H. Dammann, J. Johnson (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - GP #2093: H. Kutchai, N. Staub (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - GP #2094: H. Marita, A. Shiraishi (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - GP #2095: L. Bailey, P. Dresel (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - GP #2096: J. Foulks, F. Perry, H. Sanders (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - GP #2097: J. Foulks, F. Perry, H. Sanders (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - GP #2098: C. Slayman, C. Slayman (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - GP #2099: S. Grossberg (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - GP #3000: G. Little, W. Sleator (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - GP #3001: M. Carsten (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - GP #3002: D. MacLeod, K. Prasad (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - GP #3003: K. Prasad, D. MacLeod (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - GP #3004: K. Prasad (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - GP #3005: C. Caputo (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - GP #3006: W. DeMello, G. Matta, M. Chapeau (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - GP #3007: C. Gary Bobo, A. Solomon (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - GP #3008: T. Narahashi, J. Moore (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - GP #3009: C. Kao, A. Nishiyama (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - GP #3010: Y. Chang (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - GP #3011: R. LaForce, J. Duncan, H. Misamore (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - GP #3012: L. Mullins (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - GP #3013: P. Carroll (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - GP #3014: P. Carroll (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - GP #3015: G. Rich, R. Sha?afi, A. Romualdez, A. Solomon (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - GP #3016: E. Olson, R. Cazort (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - GP #3017: F. Hunter (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - GP #3018: A. Shiraishi, H. Morita (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - GP #3019: R. Birks, P. Burstyn, D. Firth (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - GP #3020: E. Stephenson (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - GP #3021: K. Prasad, D. MacLeod (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - GP #3022: J. Jacket (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - GP #3023: S. Hagiwara, R. Gruener, H. Hayashi, H. Sakata, A. Grinnell (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - GP #3024: L. Wei (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - GP #3025: W. Barry (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - GP #3026: G. Ling (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - GP #3027: M. Neville (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - GP #3028: F. Bauman (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - GP #3029: W. Wise, J. Archdeacon (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - GP #3030: A. Weber, R. Herz (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - GP #3031: A. Weber (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - GP #3032: S. Iwasaki, E. Florey (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - GP #3033: W. Fenn, R. Marquis (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - GP #3034: B. Hills (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - GP #3035: S. McLaughlin (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - GP #3036: A. Auerbach, M. Bennett (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - GP #3037: A. Auerbach, M. Bennett (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - GP #3038: A. Watanabe, S. Obara, T. Akiyama (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - GP #3039: T. Narahashi, J. Moore, R. Poston (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - GP #3040: F. Fuchs, E. Gertz, F. Briggs (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - GP #3041: A. Borle (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - GP #3042: A. Borle (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - GP #3043: N. Sperelakis, A. Pappano (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - GP #3044: G. McCann, J. Dill (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - GP #3045: E. Carmeliet, S. Bosteels (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - GP #3046: M. Okamoto, W. Riker (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - GP #3047: W. Dunson (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - GP #3048: D. Gilbert, G. Ehrenstein (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - GP #3049: M. Hess, R. Lian, F. Briggs (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - GP #3050: A. Kkoch (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - GP #3051: M. Alpern, S. Torii (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - GP #3053: F. Brinley (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - GP #3054: R. Whitlock, H. Wheeler (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - GP #3055: A. Strickholm, B. Wallin, P. Shrager (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - GP #3056: B. Lindley (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - GP #3057: J. Argibay, C. Caputo (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - GP #3058: G. Wasserman (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - GP #3059: G. Pilar, P. Vaughn (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - GP #3060: G. Pilar (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - GP #3061: G. Pilar, P. Vaughn (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - GP #3062: S. Takagi, H. Kitamura, K. Imai, H. Takeuchi (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - GP #3063: F. Kallus, J. Vanatta (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - GP #3064: N. Takeguchi, M. Nakagaki (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - GP #3065: Y. Naitoh, R. Eckert (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - GP #3066: Y. Naitoh, R. Eckert (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - GP #3067: M. Evans, P. Ray (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - GP #3068: L. Girardier, J. Seydoux, T. Clausen (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - GP #3069: R. Hart, M. Langham (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - GP #3070: M. Lang, H. Gainer (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - GP #3071: W. Biggley, E. Swift, R. Buchanan, H. Seliger (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - GP #3072: W. Taylor, J. Kreier (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - GP #3073: A. Politoff, S. Socolar, W. Lowenstein (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - GP #3074: S. Stoney, X. Machne (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - GP #3075: T. Andreoli, V. Dennis, A. Weigl (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - GP #3076: T. Waterman, H. Fernandez, T. Goldsmith (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - GP #3077: B. Burchill (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - GP #3078: L. Binstock, H. Lecar (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - GP #3079: K. Koketsu, S. Nishi (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - GP #3080: B. Munch, S. Schultz (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - GP #3081: R. Faust, M. Leadbetter, E. Therrien (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - GP #3082: T. Murakami, A. Zimmerman (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - GP #3083: T. Hidaka, H. Kuriyama (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - GP #3084: C. Taylor (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - GP #3085: S. Taylor, H. Preiser, A. Sandow (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - GP #3086: M. Walling, S. Rothman (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - GP #3087: J. Quay, W. Armstrong (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - GP #3088: M. Ginzberg, L. Sachs, B. Ginzberg (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - GP #3089: R. Vick, C. Hazlewood, B. Nichols (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - GP #3090: R. Josephson, M. Maclin (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - GP #3091: E. Lea (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - GP #3092: A. Goldner, S. Schultz, P. Curran (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - GP #3093: L. Kirschner (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - GP #3094: M. Fedde (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - GP #3095: S. Schultz (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - GP #3096: J. Davidson (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - GP #3097: P. Gage, R. Eisenberg (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - GP #3098: R. Eisenberg, P. Gage (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - GP #3099: P. Gage, R. Eisenberg (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - GP #3100: J. Liu (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - GP #3101: A. MacGillivray, D. Hare (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - GP #3102: A. Finn (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - GP #3103: R. Scheuplein, I. Blank (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - GP #3104: R. DeVoe, R. Small (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - GP #3105: R. Wyman (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - GP #3106: H. Fozzard, G. Dominguez (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - GP #3107: Y. Naitoh (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - GP #3108: D. Fulpis, F. Baumann (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - GP #3109: F. Romeu, A. Salibian, S. Pezzani-Hernandez (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - GP #3110: D. Dick, E. Dick, D. Tosteson (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - GP #3111: R. Bean, W. Shepherd, H. Chan, J. Eichner (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - GP #3112: L. Moore (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - GP #3113: E. Rojas, R. Taylor, I. Atwater, F. Bezanilla (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - GP #3114: S. Rapaport (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - GP #3115: N. Davids, C. Ray (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - GP #3116: L. J. Mullins, F. J. Brinley, Jr. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - GP #3117: David C. Wood (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - GP #3118: David C. Wood (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - GP #3119: David C. Wood (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - GP #3120: J. Forte, L. Limlomwongse, D. Kasbekar (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - GP #321: H. Klingberg (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - GP #3122: W. Adelman, Y. Palti (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - GP #3123: S. Hagiwara, H. Hayashi, K. Tayama (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - GP #3124: B. Wallin (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - GP #3125: A. Kleinhaus, C. Kao (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - GP #3126: A. Weber (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - GP #3127: H. Grundfest (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - GP #3128: H. Herman, M. Skiles (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - GP #3129: J. Bourgoigine, S. Klahr, J. Yates, L. Guena, N. Bricker (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - GP #3130: G. Weiss, F. Goodman (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - GP #3131: C. Paterson (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - GP #3132: R. Palmer, V. Posey (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3133: W. Dudley, S. Winegrad (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3134: D. Dick (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3135: D. Schwab, J. Scala (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3136: M. Kafka, C. Pak (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3137: S. Klahr, A. Shaw, K. Hwang, C. Miller (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3138: J. Blencher (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3139: D. Spear, J. Barr, C. Barr (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3140: G. Porter (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3141: L. Moore (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3142: A. Overman, G. Larimer, R. Miller (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3143: R. Katzman, G. Lehrer, C. Wilson (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3144: A. Watanabe, S. Obara (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3145: S. Rapaport, L. Peachey, D. Goldstein (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3145: R. Barlow (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3147: P. Vassar, M. Kendall, G. Seaman (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3148: G. Seaman, P. Vassar, M. Kendall (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3149: M. Fairbanks, J. Hoffert, P. Fromm (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3150: E. Rogus, T. Price, K. Zierler (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3151: A. Paes de Carvalho, M. De Paula Carvalho (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3152: C. Gary Bobo, R. DiPolo, A. Solomon (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3153: N. Anderson (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3154: M. Villamill, C. Kleeman (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3155: F. Bowman, E. Faulkes (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3156: A. Ables (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3157: R. Sjodin, L. Beauge (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3158: B. Kennedy (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3159: K. Dving, W. Miller (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3160: E. Bartels, D. Nachmansohn (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GP #3161: Y. Sakamoto, M. Gato (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - GP #3162: H. Hopkins, J. Sage, B. Fry (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - GP #3163: C. Armstrong (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - GP #3164: A. Borle (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - GP #3165: B. Alving (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - GP #3166: M. Jackson, M. Cassidy (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GP #3166: A. Clark, R. Millecchia, A. Mauro (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - GP #3168: R. Millecchia, A. Mauro (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - GP #3169: R. Millecchia, A. Mauro (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - GP #3170: M. Civan (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - GP #3171: P. Eggena, I. Schwartz, R. Walter (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - GP #3172: F. Motokizawa, J. Ruben, H. Grundfest (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - GP #3173: F. Fuchs, E. Gertz, F. Briggs (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - GP #3174: W. Kwant, P. Seeman (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - GP #3175: I. Fenichel, S. Horowitz (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - GP #3176: Y. Matsumoto, T. Hoekman, B. Abbott (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - GP #3177: J. Reeves, R. Dowben (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - GP #3178: H. Punke (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - GP #3179: T. Moore, B. Schlowsky, C. Yakulic (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - GP #3180: F. Varela, W. Wittanen (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - GP #3181: W. Wittanen, F. Varela (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - GP #3182: R. Shoemaker, G. Makhlouf, G. Sachs (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - GP #3183: O. Schanne (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - GP #3184: D. Gayton, R. Allen, J. Hinke (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - GP #3185: R. Rikmenspoel, S. Sinton, J. Janick (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - GP #3186: G. Borst-Pauwels, D. Goldstein (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - GP #3187: C. Kao, P. Stanfield (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - GP #3188: Y. Sakamoto (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - GP #3189: W. Adelman, Y. Plati (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - GP #3190: J. Nolte, J. Brown (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - GP #3191: E. Albuquerque, R. Mcisaac (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - GP #3192: L. Binstock, L. Goldman (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - GP #3193: L. Goldman, L. Binstock (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - GP #3194: L. Goldman, L. Binstock (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - GP #3195: E. Gordon, M. De Hartog (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - GP #3196: F. Offner (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - GP #3197: B. Curtis (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - GP #3198: A. Soll (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - GP #3199: K. S. Lee, B. C. Shin (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - GP #3200: R. Schultz, S. Asunmaa, G. Guter, F. Littman (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - GP #3201: R. Schultz, S. Asunmaa, F. Kleist (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - GP #3202: P. Horowicz, J. Taylor, D. Waggoner (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - GP #3203: R. Srinivasan, A. Kadish, R. Sridhar (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - GP #3204: J. Frazer, V. Van Breemen, P. Langlinais, C. Martin (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - GP #3205: C. Finch, H. Huberman, A. Mirsky (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - GP #3206: C. Finch, J. Foster, A. Mirsky (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - GP #3207: W. Edwards, G. Lucketic, B. Hirschowitz, G. Sachs (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - GP #3208: R. Williams (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - GP #3209: R. Williams (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - GP #3210: G. Langer, S. Serena (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - GP #3211: A. Mauro, F. Conti, F. Dodge, R. Schar (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - GP #3212: I. Fenichel, S. Horrowitz (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - GP #3213: S. Winegrad (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - GP #3214: D. Carpenter (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - GP #3215: H. Kuriyama, T. Osa, H. Tasaki (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - GP #3216: S. Bryant (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - GP #3217: G. Van Rossum (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - GP #3218: W. Sanborn, G. Langer (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - GP #3219: L. Nanninga, R. Kempen (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - GP #3220: A. Gordon, R. Godt (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - GP #3221: B. Jacobsen, B. Smith, S. Epstein (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - GP #3222: S. Basteels, A. Vleugels, A. Caremeliet (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - GP #3223: R. DiPolo, R. I. Sha'afi, A. K. Solomon (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - GP #3224: H. Levitan, L. Tauc, J. Segundo (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - GP #3225: R. H. Jacob (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - GP #3226: R. Guttman, R. Barnhill (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - GP #3227: William R. Galey, J. T. Van Bruggen (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - GP #3228: S. Wallach, P. J. Gamponia, S. A. Ahmed (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - GP #3229: A. M. Woodin, A. A. Wieneke (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - GP #3230: F. Ruiz-Manresa, A. C. Ruarte, T. L. Schwartz, H. Grundfest (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - GP #3231: L. Cuervo, W. Adelman (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - GP #3232: A. Scarpa, A. Cecchetto, G. Azzone (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - GP #3233: R. Solaro, E. Gertz, F. Briggs (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - GP #3234: M. LeFevre, J. Gennaro, W. Brodsky (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - GP #3235: M. Ginsburg, L. Sachs, B. Ginzburg (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - GP #3236: M. Ginzburg (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - GP #3237: Vincent W. Dennis, Nancy W. Stead, Thomas E. Andreoli (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - GP #3238: J. Haggar, A. Lamont, P. Curran (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - GP #3239: G. Ehrenstein, H. Lecar, R. Nassal (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - GP #3240: J. Fee, H. Edelhauser (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - GP #3241: R. Villegas, F. Barnola, G. Camejo (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - GP #3242: N. Sperelakis, G. Mayer, R. Macdonald (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - GP #3243: E. Chiarandini, J. Ruben, P. Brandt, H. Grundfest (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - GP #3244: D. Chiarandini, J. Ruben, L. Girardier, G. Katz, H. Grundfest (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - GP #3245: H. Saddler (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - GP #3246: H. Kuriyama, T. Tomita (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - GP #3247: H. Ginsburg, B. Ginzburg (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - GP #3248: A. Martonosi, P. Duggan (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - GP #3249: R. Dillion, R. Sanmartin, D. Mailman (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - GP #3250: P. Curran, J. Hajjar, I. Glynn (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - GP #3251: Ettienne (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - GP #3251: A. Johnson, H. Rothstein (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - GP #3253: A. Larkum, M. Pring (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - GP #3254: J. Gutknecht, D. Tosteson (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - GP #3255A: D. Bronk /GP #3255B: T. Bullock (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - GP #3256: R. Sha'afi, G. Rich, D. Mikulecky, A. Solomon (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - GP #3257: A. Jones (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - GP #3258: F. Vieria, R. Sha?afi, A. Solomon (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - GP #3259: W. Freygang, W. Trautwein (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - GP #3260: D. Hartshorne (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - GP #3261: R. Benolken, S. Jacobson (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - GP #3262: W. Van Der Kloot (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - GP #3263: R. Srebro, S. Yeandle (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - GP #3264: R. Eckert, Y. Naitoh (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - GP #3265: N. Telfer, L. Cornell, J. Prescott (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - GP #3266: M. Endoh, K. Hashimoto (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - GP #3267: P. Nobel (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - GP #3268: R. Eisenberg, E. Engel (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - GP #3269: C. Slayman, C. Slayman (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - GP #3270: W. Nastuk, R. Parsons (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - GP #3271: H. Lorkovic (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - GP #3272: H. Lorkovic (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - GP #3273: H. Larkovic (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - GP #3274: C. A. Rotunno, F. A. Vilallonga, M. Fernandez, M. Creijido (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - GP #3275: Y. Ito, Y. Sakamoto, H. Kuriyama (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - GP #3276: Y. Sakamoto, H. Kuriyama (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - GP #3277: J. Sachs (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - GP #3278: Y. Sakamoto, H. Kuriyama (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - GP #3279: D. Lambert, R. Parsons (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - GP #3280: A. Borle, E. Herald (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - GP #3281: M. Mozell (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - GP #3282: J. Russell, A. Brown (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - GP #3283: L. Costantin (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - GP #3284: A. Brown, P. Berman (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - GP #3285: A. Brown, J. Walker, R. Sutton (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - GP #3286: E. Henderson, S. Walkenstein (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - GP #3287: J. Nalte, J. Brown (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - GP #3288: J. Schultz (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - GP #3289: A. Cass, A. Finklestein, V. Krespi (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - GP #3290: R. Halz, A. Finklestein (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - GP #3291: L. Goldman, L. Binstock (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - GP #3292: H. Bar, O. Hechter, I. Schwartz, R. Walter (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - GP #3293: D. Gilbert, G. Eherenstein (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - GP #3294: P. De Weer (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - GP #3295: G. Taylor, D. Paton, E. Daniel (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - GP #3296: K. Muller, J. Brown, G. Murray (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - GP #3297: J. Stewart, H. Levy (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - GP #3298: J. Chapman, C. Gibbs (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - GP #3299: J. Chapman, C. Gibbs (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - GP #3300: M. Stepita-Klauco, E. Giacobini (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - GP #3301: M. Stepita-Klauco, S. Havmark, E. Giacobini (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - GP #3302: P. Stein (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - GP #3303: J. Hinke (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - GP #3304: C. Gibb s, W. Gibbson (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - GP #3305: A. Suria, L. Hurwitz (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - GP #3306: S. Iwasaki, K. Satow (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - GP #3307: S. Batra, E. Daniel (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - GP #3308: S. Batra, E. Daniel (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - GP #3309: D. Landowne (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - GP #3310: L. Cedrini, A. Ferroni, D. Lovisolo (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - GP #3311: R. Epstein, H. Grundfest (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - GP #3312: C. Sontag (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - GP #3313: P. Sokolove, I. Cooke (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - GP #3314: P. Sokolove (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - GP #3315: P. Sokolove, I. Cooke (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - GP #3316: P. Sokolove, I. Cooke (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - GP #3317: J. Higgins (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - GP #3318: T. Biber, P. Curran (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - GP #3319: A. Manthey (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - GP #3320: A. Sorenson (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - GP #3321: M. Singer (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - GP #3322: L. Moore (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - GP #3323: V. Lange, R. Lange, A. Solomon (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - GP #3324: A. Moawad, E. Daniel (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - GP #3325: H. Spekrijse, A. Norton (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - GP #3326: M. Petzuch, M. Delbruck (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - GP #3327: E. Forker (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - GP #3328: C. Patlak, S. Raporport (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - GP #3329: J. Sachs (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - GP #3330: J. McReynolds, A. Gorman (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - GP #3331: J. McReynolds, A. Gorman (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - GP #3332: M. Schneider (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - GP #3333: G. Strother, A. Casella (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - GP #3334: N. Otto, J. Quinn (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - GP #3335: R. Frizzell, S. Schultz (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - GP #3336: A. Granada, S. Yazalla (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - GP #3337: C. Paterson, D. Maurice (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - GP #3338: T. Kerstetter, L. Kirschner, D. Rafuse (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - GP #3339: R. L. Parsons, E. W. Johnson, D. H. Lambert (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - GP #3340: R. Meiss (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - GP #3341: J. Dawling, H. Ripps (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - GP #3342: T. Andreoli, S. Troutman (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - GP #3343: T. Andreoli, J. Shafer, S. Troutman (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - GP #3344: K. Shine, S. Serena, G. Langer (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - GP #3345: A. Thorhaug (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - GP #3346: G. Manning (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - GP #3347: A. Shiraishi, M. Kuwabara (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - GP #3348: B. Saucek (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - GP #3349: S. Schultz, L. Yu-Tu, O. Alverez, P. Curran (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - GP #3350: B. Knight, J. Toyoda, F. Dodge (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - GP #3351: I. Miller (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - GP #3352: D. Wheeler, L. Bayarsky (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - GP #3353: E. Page, B. Mobley, M. Lewis, J. Upshaw (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - GP #3354: R. Dehaan (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - GP #3355: D. Wilson (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - GP #3356: S. Yamagishi, H. Grundfest (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - GP #3357: T. Saito (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - GP #3358: R. A. Sjodin (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - GP #3359: M. Brust, S. Toback, J. R. Bedine, N. Godzama (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - GP #3360: Peter F. Curran (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - GP #3361: T. Akiyama, H. Grundfest (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - GP #3362: Norman W. Robie, Sidney W. Beckett (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - GP #3363: N. Kayama, K. Kurihara (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - GP #3364: J. Mittenthall, F. Carlson (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - GP #3365: J. Mittenthall, F. Carlson (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - GP #3366: J. Shibata (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - GP #3369: A. Weber (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - GP #3367: E. C. Vas, G. B. Frank (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - GP #3368: E. C. Vas, G. B. Frank (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - GP #3370: A. Weber (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - GP #3371: F. Vieira, S. Caplan, A. Essing (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - GP #3372: F. Vieira, S. Caplan, A. Essing (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - GP #3373: B. A. Curtis (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - GP #3374: Arselio P. Carvalho, Amilcar M. Mata (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - GP #3375: Daniel Johnson, R. Igor Gamow (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - GP #3376: D. Easton (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - GP #3377: D. Easton, K. Taysi (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - GP #3378: G. Giebisch, S. Weidman (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - GP #3379: Michael A. Singer, Howard S. Frazier (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - GP #3380: Edward G. Henderson (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - GP #3381: Young N. Cha, Bak C. Shin, Kwang S. Lee (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - GP #3382: Arthur L. Finn, Maxine L. Rockoff (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - GP #3383: Arthur L. Finn (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - GP #3384: Charlotte M. Mistretta (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - GP #3385: P. Sokolove, I. Cooke (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - GP #3386: A. Mauro, A. Freeman, J. Cooley, A. Cass (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - GP #3387: B. Mobley, E. Page (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - GP #3388: S. Bloom (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - GP #3389: G. Taylor, D. Paton, E. Daniel (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - GP #3390: L. Coben, E. Cotlier, C. Beaty, B. Becker (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - GP #3391: E. Robin, J. Smith, J. Adamson, B. Packer, A. Tanser, J. Millen (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - GP #3392: F. Ruiz-Manresa, H. Grundfest (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - GP #3393: E. Robin, M. Murdaugh Jr., C. Cross, J. Theodore, J. Smith (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - GP #3394: E. Hunter, T. McDonald, D. MacLeod (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - GP #3395: T. Strunk (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - GP #3396: J. Reuben, P. Brandt, M. Berman, H. Grundfest (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - GP #3397: J. Howell, P. Vaughn, R. Eisenberg (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - GP #3398: C. Gary-Bobo, A. Solomon (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - GP #3399: E. Hayes, R. Kuchler (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - GP #3400: T. Andreoli, D. Tosteson (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - GP #3401: M. Wiederholt, W. Sullivan, P. Curran, G. Grebisch, A. Solomon (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - GP #3402: D. Cremaschi, S. Henin, M. Calvi (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - GP #3403: W. Stratten, T. Ogden (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - GP #3403: I. Singer, M. Civan (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - GP #3045: R. Shapley (Box 23, Folder 30)